wefbee.com 2017-12-28

# WefBee - Auto Group Poster | Auto Page Poster | Autoliker | Auto-Commenter | Fb Status Via

> Personal information which we are collected is used to help make your visit to our site more enjoyable and productive. We takes the guarantee of confidentiality of personal data of users of our website. We use all personal data relating to members, visitors or customers of our website will be handled in accordance with the Law on Personal Data Protection, on October 26th, 1998 (Act no. 67/98).  
> 
> 
> ###  **What we collect from user of our website ?**
> 
> Personal information collected include your name, email address, date of birth and others.The use of our website implies the acceptance of our Privacy Statement. The Wefbee Team have the right to change this agreement at any time without any notice. Therefore, to stay updated, we recommend you to check our privacy policy periodically.  
> We do not sell, trade and rent your personal information(access token) to other website or individual. We are using your token to access your facebook groups and pages.  
>    
> 
> 
> ###  Changes in privacy policy
> 
> We recommend our website users to periodically check this page for any changes to stay updated about how we are protect the personal information which we collects. It is your responsibility to review and agree our privacy policy.  
>    
> 
> 
> ###  Links to other websites
> 
> Our website may contain links of other websites in your interest. These are the google adsense ads. Once you have click on these links to leave our site, please note that we do not have any control over on other website. Therefore, we will not be responsible for the privacy and protection  of any information which you provide to other such sites. 

## What our clients say

> Best multi group poster site I have ever use.
> 
> Krystian Wojcik

> When I use Fb Status Via tool, my friends thinks I have all expensive mobiles.
> 
> Joseph Wanjau

> With you autoliker I get 1000+ likes on my all photos.
> 
> Tony Reis

> Thanks for providing awesome auto group poster in free. With the help of your group poster I gives 5,000 daily traffic to my website.
> 
> William Smith

#### About Us

Wefbee is a Facebook Auto Group Poster, Auto Page Poster, Autoliker, Auto-Commenter, Bot liker/commenter, Fb Status via tools website. You can share post in multiple groups or pages in single click with our Auto Group Poster and Auto Page Poster. Also you can update your facebook status via expensive phones.

Click here..!! to read more About Us.
